<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Quant Lab</title>
  
  <subtitle>“Learn the rules like a pro, so you can break them like an artist.”</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-01-15T03:08:57.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Joe Zhou</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>First post</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/01/15/First-post/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/01/15/First-post/</id>
    <published>2018-01-15T01:51:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-01-15T03:08:57.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I work with data. In daytime, I provide my modelling and (basic) IT skills to a hedge fund. After work, my interests include swimming, indoor rock climbing and reading. I learned swimming at the age of 5, and received strict training in my primary school. This experience benefited me a lot, which helped me overcome asthma, and let me know good performance is always related to good training. In terms of reading, luckily, having a thorough knowledge structure of statistical learning and absorbing it into my brain model is not only my personal interests, it also benefits my work. So, in some extent, my hobbies allow me to do that for a living.</p><blockquote><p>“Learn the rules like a pro, so you can break them like an artist.”</p></blockquote><p>To perform like a pro, there are many to learn. A qualified quant should also be a full stack engineer with the knowledge of mathematics, statistics, and computer science.</p><p>I decide to write something, to record my ideas and progress, moreover, to organise my thoughts. A long-term target is like marathon running, if I do not break it down into several TODOs, it would be a struggle.</p><p>Some interesting topics to be covered in 2018:</p><ul><li>Review of econometrics</li><li>Review of linear model</li><li>high performance real-time computation</li><li>cryptocurrency trading</li></ul>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;I work with data. In daytime, I provide my modelling and (basic) IT skills to a hedge fund. After work, my interests include swimming, in
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="2018, first post" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/2018-first-post/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
